<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-12T23:22:45+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Chicken On A Bun</title><subtitle>Chicken On A Bun is a curated guide to the best fried chicken sandwiches in America. We traveled and visited every restaurant listed and thoroughly taste tested the chicken sandwiches and sides so you can enjoy the good ones.</subtitle><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><entry><title type="html">Tender Greens</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/09/04/tender-greens.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tender Greens" /><published>2022-09-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2022/09/04/tender-greens</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/09/04/tender-greens.html"><![CDATA[<p>Famous for their greens and salads, Tender Greens also offers a fried chicken sandwich. Disappointingly though, the
chicken was not fried to order but just sitting under a warming lamp in the open kitchen area. This resulted in a
slightly dry piece of chicken with the taste being good for white chicken meat. The sandwich also comes with cabbage
slaw and pickles which balanced out the very tasty and slightly spicy chili mayo. The chili mayo was the second best
part of this sandwich, right after the fluffy and fresh brioche bun.</p>

<p>On the side you have many good and somewhat healthy choices. The fingerling potatoes are pretty good but definitely have
a look at their seasonal vegetables. The vegetables can be hit or miss but when we were there, they had a very tasty
medley of perfectly grilled summer squash, mushrooms, and green beans.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famous for their greens and salads, Tender Greens also offers a fried chicken sandwich. Disappointingly though, the chicken was not fried to order but just sitting under a warming lamp in the open kitchen area. This resulted in a slightly dry piece of chicken with the taste being good for white chicken meat. The sandwich also comes with cabbage slaw and pickles which balanced out the very tasty and slightly spicy chili mayo. The chili mayo was the second best part of this sandwich, right after the fluffy and fresh brioche bun.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/tender-greens.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/tender-greens.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sur at the Barnyard</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/30/sur-at-the-barnyard.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sur at the Barnyard" /><published>2022-03-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/30/sur-at-the-barnyard</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/30/sur-at-the-barnyard.html"><![CDATA[<p>Besides the sandwich at <a href="/2019/12/07/the-table.html">The Table</a>, this might be the largest one we had so far.
It was so large, it broke apart while eating. I also didn’t feel great afterwards because it was so much food. The
chicken was good and juicy, with a nice crisp on the outside. On the list of negative points, the sauce on the sandwich
didn’t have much flavor and there was just wayyy too much lettuce on this sandwich. Like cheap iceberg lettuce, nothing
fancy. But on the upside, they have this amazing thick bacon that you should add on your chicken sandwich. Or order it
as a side. The bacon rescued this mediocre chicken sandwich.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides the sandwich at The Table, this might be the largest one we had so far. It was so large, it broke apart while eating. I also didn’t feel great afterwards because it was so much food. The chicken was good and juicy, with a nice crisp on the outside. On the list of negative points, the sauce on the sandwich didn’t have much flavor and there was just wayyy too much lettuce on this sandwich. Like cheap iceberg lettuce, nothing fancy. But on the upside, they have this amazing thick bacon that you should add on your chicken sandwich. Or order it as a side. The bacon rescued this mediocre chicken sandwich.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/sur-at-the-barnyard.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/sur-at-the-barnyard.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Zareen’s</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/26/zareens.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Zareen’s" /><published>2022-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/26/zareens</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/26/zareens.html"><![CDATA[<p>There are a lot of things to like about Zareen’s and you should definitely visit no matter what you order. So when they
put the Crispy Chicken Tikka Sandwich on their menu, we were ecstatic. They describe it as extra crispy, extra juicy and
they’re not lying. The piece of chicken is super juicy and incorporates lots of their trademark flavors. The pickles and
the sauce have a tang that pairs very well with the chicken. You can also add jalapenos and cheese on that sandwich.
While the cheese is not very exciting, we can recommend adding the jalapenos.</p>

<p>The only reason holding this back from a full 10 chicken score is that the bread is very sweet and mushy. But we’ll be
back for this sandwich. Especially since it’s paired with their amazing Masala Fries which are crispy thin fries
sprinkled with a masala spice blend.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of things to like about Zareen’s and you should definitely visit no matter what you order. So when they put the Crispy Chicken Tikka Sandwich on their menu, we were ecstatic. They describe it as extra crispy, extra juicy and they’re not lying. The piece of chicken is super juicy and incorporates lots of their trademark flavors. The pickles and the sauce have a tang that pairs very well with the chicken. You can also add jalapenos and cheese on that sandwich. While the cheese is not very exciting, we can recommend adding the jalapenos.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/zareens.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/zareens.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">KFC</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/06/kfc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KFC" /><published>2022-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/06/kfc</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/03/06/kfc.html"><![CDATA[<p>The KFC chicken sandwich is basically a copy of the <a href="/2020/04/10/popeyes.html">Popeyes sandwich</a>. It’s pretty
good so we’re giving it the same rating. It slightly beats the
<a href="/2021/07/03/burger-king.html">Burger King sandwich</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The KFC chicken sandwich is basically a copy of the Popeyes sandwich. It’s pretty good so we’re giving it the same rating. It slightly beats the Burger King sandwich.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/kfc.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/kfc.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cowboy Bar &amp;amp; Grill</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/02/26/cowboy-bar-grill.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cowboy Bar &amp;amp; Grill" /><published>2022-02-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2022/02/26/cowboy-bar-grill</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2022/02/26/cowboy-bar-grill.html"><![CDATA[<p>The Cowboy Bar &amp; Grill had a fried chicken sandwich as a special so we had to try it. Unfortunately it wasn’t very good
and we should’ve stuck to one of their juicy burgers. The piece of chicken was extremely tough and dry, almost hard to
eat. The flavor was pretty good though with a spicy glaze on the chicken.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cowboy Bar &amp; Grill had a fried chicken sandwich as a special so we had to try it. Unfortunately it wasn’t very good and we should’ve stuck to one of their juicy burgers. The piece of chicken was extremely tough and dry, almost hard to eat. The flavor was pretty good though with a spicy glaze on the chicken.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/cowboy-bar-grill.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/cowboy-bar-grill.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Hen House</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/12/05/hen-house.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hen House" /><published>2021-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2021/12/05/hen-house</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/12/05/hen-house.html"><![CDATA[<p>We stopped here while driving hungry through Danville, and this is a great fried chicken sandwich spot. The bun is nice
and fluffy and the meat is what it should be for a good sandwich. By default it comes with dark meat (that’s what we
went for) but you can also “upgrade” to white meat for $2. Pair the sandwich with some of their tasty garlic fries and
you got yourself an excellent lunch, served to you by the friendly staff of Hen House. There were only two things to
criticize here: the chicken was slightly greasy, and the sauce was not very flavorful – otherwise two enthusiastic
thumbs up!</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We stopped here while driving hungry through Danville, and this is a great fried chicken sandwich spot. The bun is nice and fluffy and the meat is what it should be for a good sandwich. By default it comes with dark meat (that’s what we went for) but you can also “upgrade” to white meat for $2. Pair the sandwich with some of their tasty garlic fries and you got yourself an excellent lunch, served to you by the friendly staff of Hen House. There were only two things to criticize here: the chicken was slightly greasy, and the sauce was not very flavorful – otherwise two enthusiastic thumbs up!]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/hen-house.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/hen-house.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Baba’s Hot Chicken</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/11/26/babas-hot-chicken.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baba’s Hot Chicken" /><published>2021-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2021/11/26/babas-hot-chicken</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/11/26/babas-hot-chicken.html"><![CDATA[<p>Baba’s Hot Chicken gets only a 4/10 from us. While the chicken piece was pretty juicy, the powder that seasoned the
chicken was not very flavorful. There was an overwhelming smokiness from the seasoning and not in a good way - think one
or two too many tablespoons of smoked paprika. Various spice levels were just different chili powders on top of the
chicken. Get the “small size” which consists of one chicken tender on the sandwich. The “normal size” has two tenders
and is simply too much chicken for the sandwich.</p>

<p>The two things setting this spot apart are the sauce (pretty good) and the 9/10 fries. The fries are definitely the
highlight and you should definitely get some with your sandwich.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baba’s Hot Chicken gets only a 4/10 from us. While the chicken piece was pretty juicy, the powder that seasoned the chicken was not very flavorful. There was an overwhelming smokiness from the seasoning and not in a good way - think one or two too many tablespoons of smoked paprika. Various spice levels were just different chili powders on top of the chicken. Get the “small size” which consists of one chicken tender on the sandwich. The “normal size” has two tenders and is simply too much chicken for the sandwich.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/babas-hot-chicken.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/babas-hot-chicken.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Hideout</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/09/18/the-hideout.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Hideout" /><published>2021-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2021/09/18/the-hideout</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/09/18/the-hideout.html"><![CDATA[<p>The Hideout is a small American restaurant in the woods of Aptos. In the Sandwich &amp; Burger section of their menu is a
fried chicken sandwich. It’s a basic sandwich with slaw, pickle slices, a chipotle aioli. While the potato bun was
pretty good, the chicken piece was disappointing - small and not very crispy. Overall, the sandwich was slightly on the
dry side and not particularly memorable.</p>

<p>They have fantastic truffle fries with parmesan though, so get some of that and pair it with their spicy aioli or some
ranch dressing.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hideout is a small American restaurant in the woods of Aptos. In the Sandwich &amp; Burger section of their menu is a fried chicken sandwich. It’s a basic sandwich with slaw, pickle slices, a chipotle aioli. While the potato bun was pretty good, the chicken piece was disappointing - small and not very crispy. Overall, the sandwich was slightly on the dry side and not particularly memorable.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/the-hideout.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/the-hideout.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Orchard City Kitchen</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/09/04/orchard-city-kitchen.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Orchard City Kitchen" /><published>2021-09-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2021/09/04/orchard-city-kitchen</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/09/04/orchard-city-kitchen.html"><![CDATA[<p>Crispy crispy crispy! This fried chicken sandwich from the Brunch menu is crispy! We’ve never had such a satisfyingly
crunchy cornflake-based breading - it simply breaks apart with every bite. The sandwich came with two thin pieces of
chicken which were very juicy on the inside. The sandwich was pretty standard in terms of ingredients and well executed:
nice bun, spicy mayo, and pickle slices in addition to a juicy pickle spear on the side.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crispy crispy crispy! This fried chicken sandwich from the Brunch menu is crispy! We’ve never had such a satisfyingly crunchy cornflake-based breading - it simply breaks apart with every bite. The sandwich came with two thin pieces of chicken which were very juicy on the inside. The sandwich was pretty standard in terms of ingredients and well executed: nice bun, spicy mayo, and pickle slices in addition to a juicy pickle spear on the side.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/orchard-city-kitchen.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/orchard-city-kitchen.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Screen Door</title><link href="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/08/08/screen-door.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Screen Door" /><published>2021-08-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-12T23:16:57+00:00</updated><id>https://chickenonabun.com/2021/08/08/screen-door</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://chickenonabun.com/2021/08/08/screen-door.html"><![CDATA[<p>We can be a little skeptical when there’s a significant wait for any restaurant - after all, that’s how they always get
you, right? With an hour long wait and swarms of people waiting outside? Nonetheless, our brunch experience at the
Screen Door in Portland did not disappoint.</p>

<p>The fried chicken sandwich was perfection, sizable yet not too big, striking a delicate balance with a large piece of
crispy chicken, a heap of creamy slaw, and a light and fresh bun. The sandwich was not spicy yet delivered big flavor.
With a menu for fried chicken and non-fried chicken lovers (do these people exist???) alike, this place is definitely
worth the stop if you’re ever in town.</p>]]></content><author><name>COAB Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can be a little skeptical when there’s a significant wait for any restaurant - after all, that’s how they always get you, right? With an hour long wait and swarms of people waiting outside? Nonetheless, our brunch experience at the Screen Door in Portland did not disappoint.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/screen-door.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://chickenonabun.com/assets/images/medium/screen-door.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>